(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ 販売期間 1.14 20:00 - 2.24 18:00
2nd Round Sales Goods. Sales Period: Jan 14, 20:00 - Feb 24, 18:00.
Attention: ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all guests attending
照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights / Loud cheering is OK
2次販売グッズ グッズ販売期間 ~2.24 18:00
2nd Round Goods Sale: Available until Feb 24, 18:00
だから
So...
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you!
あふれるこの気持ち きっと止まらない
These overflowing feelings surely won't stop.
Ai Ai Ai Ai I love you
君が Ai Ai Ai Ai I need you
You are... Ai Ai Ai Ai I need you
もっと...
More...
動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for the videos!
ぜひ『あいあいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー』を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Please try making a video using 'Ai Ai Ai Ai Love You'!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
夢見るハートがピョンピョンピョン
My dreaming heart goes hop hop hop
沼に落ちてアビャビャビャ
Falling into the swamp going abya-bya-bya
こんなになっても未だ
Even after becoming like this, I still
抜け出せない (Hey!)
Can't escape (Hey!)
どうしたものかの ぬいぬいぬい
What to do, nui-nui-nui
助けて君たち アホイホイ
Help me, everyone, Ahoy-hoy
待った 待った 待った 待った
Wait, wait, wait, wait
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got hooked on anime and now I want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Watching my favorite scenes...
カラオケ歌えるなんて
I can't believe I can sing karaoke with them!
尊すぎてツラいっ！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find the songs we want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
全国のアミューズメント施設にて
At amusement facilities nationwide,
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet Plushies,
寝そべりミニマスコット
Lying Down Mini Mascots,
大判マウスパッド
Large Mousepads.
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide!
詳しくは...
For more details...
キャラ広場
Chara Hiroba!
FuRyu
吉野家でご・は・ん・しよ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya!
牛
Beef.
牛牛
Beef, beef.
牛っ
Beef!
うまっ
Yum.
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Enjoy the original's dedication.
牛丼は吉野家
Beef bowls are Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれな
This is the one.
ホロライブ3期生 ミニCDコレクションが登場！
Hololive 3rd Generation Mini CD Collection is here!
ガシャポン！
Gashapon!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は、ホロライブ...
Today, Hololive...
さあ、ホロライブ 3rd Generation Live 「きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Now, thank you for coming to the Hololive 3rd Generation Live 'Kyururun Operation: The Strongest Idol, You Have to Stan, Right?'!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live to the very end, let me provide some guidance.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of video recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
The venue is non-smoking. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど...
Acts such as mosh pits, diving, throwing objects onto the stage...
...他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
...and anything that annoys others or interferes with the performance is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a blast!
あー、すごいね、聞こえるね。うん。
Ah, amazing, I can hear you. Yeah.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り...
Also, please be aware that cameras for video distribution and photography will be in the venue...
...客席が映り込む場合があります。
...and the audience seating may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので...
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotions and similar purposes...
...あらかじめご了承ください。
...so we ask for your understanding in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#きゅるるん大作戦DAY2」です。
Also, the hashtag for the live is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY2.
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてください！盛り上げてね！
Please use the hashtag and hype it up a lot! Hype it up!
それでは開演まであと少しです。
Well then, it's just a little while until the show starts.
君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください！
Let us hear your voices loud and clear!
そして！今からちょっと3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが...
And! We, the 3rd Generation, are thinking of doing a huddle right now...
えっと、マイクを通さずやりますので、ちょっと静かにして... 耳を澄ませていただきまして...
Um, we'll do it without microphones, so please be quiet... and listen carefully...
はい、行くんで、ちょっとシーンと待っててくださいね。
Okay, we're going to do it, so please wait in silence.
行きます。
Here we go.
こんぺこ！
Kon-peko!
こんぬい！
Kon-nui!
こんまっする！
Kon-muscle!
Ahoy!
超アイドル電脳ガールは欲張り
Super idol cyber girls are greedy.
笑い合って もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we become even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
遠いようで近くて
Seeming far, but actually close,
他人なのに家族みたいで
Strangers, yet like a family.
ウェブの大行進 狂い咲きセッション
A grand web parade, a blooming session.
喜怒哀楽をシェアしてさ
Sharing all our emotions together.
でっかくなって行きたいよね
We want to keep getting bigger, right?
でもちっちゃな事も大事にして
But cherishing the small things too,
一つ一つ刻んだ
Carving them one by one.
楽しんでくれるのが楽しいって
It's fun just seeing you have fun,
ただのエンターテイメント！
It's pure entertainment!
後ろまで見えてる
I can see all the way to the back!
画面の向こうも届いてる
Reaching everyone beyond the screen too!
光の海を泳ぐの
Swimming in this sea of lights!
超アイドル電脳ガールは欲張り
Super idol cyber girls are greedy.
愛されたいし 夢見せたいし
Want to be loved, want to show you dreams,
君とじゃなきゃヤダ
I don't want it if it's not with you.
絶好調です 狙い撃ちで
I'm in top form, taking aim,
君にウィンク
Winking right at you.
やっぱ電脳ガールでめっちゃハッピー
Being a cyber girl makes me super happy.
あれもしたいし これもしたいし
Want to do this, want to do that,
叶えちゃう やった！
Gonna make it all come true, yay!
全速力走る
Running at full speed,
もちろん君と
With you, of course.
笑い合って もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we become even cuter.
Oh yeah yeah
せっかくだから
Since we're here,
やりきりたいし
I want to give it my all,
乗り越えるべき壁もデカい
Even if the walls to overcome are huge.
トライ＆エラーで
Through trial and error,
君が思ってるよりずっと
Much more than you think,
君のこと想ってる
I'm thinking of you.
どうかな？
How is it?
焦がれた？
Did you yearn for it?
夢には近づけてるかな？
Am I getting closer to the dream?
声の波があるから
Because I have these waves of voices,
頑張れるんだ 聴かせて
I can keep going. Let me hear you!
One Two Three Four!
もう最高 電脳ガールは幸せ
Simply the best, cyber girls are happy.
愛されていて 寄り添いあって
Being loved, snuggling close together,
下向くとかヤダ
I refuse to look down.
テンポアップし 続けていく
Boosting the tempo, we'll keep going,
見たい景色へ
Towards the scenery we want to see.
世界 揺らして
Shake the world!
限界より断然
Far beyond the limits,
今すぐ挑戦
Challenging it right now.
みんなで作ってく
Creating it together with everyone.
Oh yeah!
どこまでも盛り上がっていくぞ！
We're gonna get hyped all the way!
君たち！
You guys!
まだまだ声 出せますよね？！
You can still scream louder, right?!
自信揺らいでも頑張っちゃう
褒められて伸びるわかってるよね
Even if my confidence wavers, I'll do my best.
You know I grow when praised, right?
この歌が宝物
なっちゃわないよ 笑
This song is my treasure.
I won't just get used to it, lol.
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドル伝説が始まるわ
The super idol legend begins!
欲張り
I'm greedy.
愛されたいし 夢見てみたい
I want to be loved, I want to dream.
君とじゃなきゃ ヤダ
I don't want it if it's not with you.
やっぱ天下統一？
As expected, world domination?
狙い撃ちで君にウインク
Sniper shot! A wink just for you.
やっぱ天のガールで めっちゃハッピー
As expected of a heavenly girl, super happy!
あれもしたいし これもしたいし
I want to do this, and I want to do that!
叶っちゃう ヤッター！
It's coming true, yay!
全力走る
Running at full power.
もちろん君と 笑い合っても
Of course, even if we laugh together with you.
とか言いながら
While saying things like that...
どこまででも 行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere!
Oh yeah yeah!
今日はこのまま さよならじゃないよ
Today isn't just a goodbye like this.
手を取ってくれたなら
If you take my hand...
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
On a night where even secrets fall asleep...
君を連れてくよ
I'll take you with me.
それはたとえば 遠く離れてたって
Even if, for example, we are far apart...
手を繋いでられるような
...as if we could still hold hands.
奇跡のような話をしよう
Let's talk about something like a miracle.
窓は開けといて
Leave the window open.
今日までを思い出して
Remembering everything up to today...
ひとつひとつ並べたら
...if we line them up one by one...
明日の雨が気になりだして
...I start to worry about tomorrow's rain.
どうも眠れないみたいだ
It seems I can't sleep somehow.
変わりたくないことや
Things I don't want to change...
変わらなきゃいけないことも
...and things that must change.
少し忘れたまま
While forgetting them a little...
窓の外 眺めていたんだ
...I was gazing out the window.
雨が降り出すその前に
Before the rain starts falling...
君のところまで行けるような気がして
...I feel like I can make it to where you are.
目を閉じてみたんだ
I tried closing my eyes.
そしてこのまま 遠くへと行こう
And so, let's go far away just like this.
手を取ってくれるかな
Will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Through the night where even secrets fall asleep...
君と泳いでいくよ
...I'll swim through it with you.
街の明かりが消える度に笑って
Laughing every time the town lights go out...
路地裏で抱き合おう
...let's embrace in the back alley.
馬鹿みたいな話をしよう
Let's talk about silly things.
窓は開けといて
Leave the window open.
聞こえる？
Can you hear it?
次はマリン！
Next is Marine!
君達！ いつまでも盛り上がっていきますよ！
You guys! Let's keep the hype going forever!
いくわよ マリン！
Let's go, Marine!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like?!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
なんとかなんないかな
Can't something be done?
ラビラビ
Lovey-dovey.
隣のあいつが邪魔だな
That guy next to me is in the way.
よくない？そんなこと
Isn't that fine? Such things.
ダメダメだ
No no no!
先手必勝絶対
First strike wins, absolutely.
童話とは違うな
It's not like a fairy tale.
なんだって競争
Everything's a competition.
君が好き そういうの
You like that? That sort of thing.
なんだか寂しい
It's somehow lonely.
気持ちは中心
Feelings are the center.
メインディッシュ？ チープな？
Main dish? Is it cheap?
あれとこれとどっち？
This one or that one, which?
あの子には負けない
I won't lose to her.
今だってジェラシー
Even now, I feel jealousy.
欲張りね 欲張りか？
Greedy, huh? Are you greedy?
してやります！
I'll do it!
ああ 言わなきゃってわかってる
Ah, I know I have to say it.
ああでもないこうでもない やめにしましょう
Not like this, not like that... let's stop this.
貫け！ My My My My
Pierce through! My My My My!
引きたくない！ 言い訳はない！
I don't want to pull back! No excuses!
時間がない？ 優柔不断！
No time? Indecisive!
だんだん？ ハニーバニーダーリンダーリン？
Gradually? Honey bunny darling darling?
マジな話
Serious talk:
どっち？ どっち？ が好きなのよ！
Which? Which? Do you like!
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで
No no no, don't look away.
ダメダメダメ 振り向かせたい
No no no, I want to make you look at me.
今は私の方でしょうでしょう？
Right now it's my turn, right right?
どうしてなんで？ 反対方向！
Why, why? Wrong direction!
Wanted!
言い訳なに？ 示談だのゆうちゅう？
What's your excuse? Settlement? You too?
ふざけんなって
Don't mess with me.
ハニバニダリダリ マジな話
Honey bunny, darling darling, serious talk,
どっちのほうが好きなのよ
which one do you like better?
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで
No no no, don't look away.
もう逃げ出したい？ でもやるしかない
Want to run away already? But you have to do it.
一緒にちゃんとしなさい 反対方向
Get it together with me! Wrong direction!
WANTED!
言い訳まり...！あーー！
Excuse Mari...! Aaaah!
そばにいて 言い訳なに... あぁ...
Stay by my side. What's your excuse... Ah...
次はぺこら！
Next is Pekora!
全力ジャンピング！いくぺこー！
Full power jumping! Let's go peko!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
どこへ吹く風 当てもなく
Where does the wind blow? Aimlessly.
歌いながら 気の向く方へ
Singing as I go, wherever I feel like.
迷ってるの？ 冒険してるの？
Are you lost? Are you adventuring?
それはみんな次第
That's up to everyone.
まだまだ楽しみたい
I still want to have fun!
でもでも時間がない
But, but, there's no time!
わふわふする明日へ
To the fluffy tomorrow,
思い切って ハリキッて 前向いて さあ進もう
boldly, enthusiastically, facing forward, let's go!
いつだって本気で
Always serious,
言い尽くしちゃえ
say it all!
It's All Right!
早起きよりも
Better than waking up early,
夜更かし O-O
staying up late O-O!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
A pinch becomes a chance.
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible.
なんだって全力で
Everything with full power,
突き抜けちゃって
break through it!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings.
Hop Step Jumpで飛び出そう
Let's jump out with a Hop Step Jump!
なかなかお布団から出られない日もある
There are days when it's hard to get out of the futon.
でも明日から そう明日から
But from tomorrow, yes from tomorrow,
本気を出すんだ
I'll get serious!
日が暮れるまで
Until the sun sets,
気が触れるまで
until I go crazy,
無限ループして
loop infinitely!
It's All Right!
早起きよりも
Better than waking up early,
夜更かし O-O
staying up late O-O!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
A pinch becomes a chance.
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible.
なんだって全力で
Everything with full power,
突き抜けちゃって
break through it!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings.
Hop Step Jumpで飛び出そう
Let's jump out with a Hop Step Jump!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
最後はノエル！
Last is Noel!
はーいみんな！しゃくれメガネ...
Ha-i everyone! Chin-glasses...
最後まで盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's get hyped until the end!
苦い恋の果て 残された
Left behind at the end of a bitter love,
出どころ不明の金の山
a mountain of money of unknown origin.
あいつの気配がするものは
Everything that feels like him
未練ばかりで食えやしない
is just regret, inedible.
あたしは生きながら化けて出る
I transform while I'm still alive.
鏡の前で早変わり
A quick change in front of the mirror.
パイパイ仮面でどうかしら
How about Pai Pai Kamen?
今宵も一暴れ
Another rampage tonight.
踊れ 踊り 踊れ
Dance, dance, dance!
乱れ髪 弾む胸
Disheveled hair, bouncing chest.
匿名の罠に酔いしれて
Drunk on the trap of anonymity.
Shine a spot
Shine a spotlight on me now
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai Pai-Pai Pai-Pai-Pai Yap-Pai
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Pai Pai Kamen is a millionaire.
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai Pai-Pai Pai-Pai-Pai Yap-Pai
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Soar, golden butterfly!
ほらほら踊れよ
Come on, dance!
散財万歳コインシャワー
Hurray for squandering! Coin shower!
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the moment!
瞬間クライマックス
Instant climax!
浮世忘れて耽る
Indulge, forgetting the floating world.
ダンシングハイ パイヤパイヤ
Dancing high, Pai-ya Pai-ya
Discotheque queen あぁパイパイ仮面
Discotheque queen, ah, Pai Pai Kamen.
パイ パパパイ パパパヤッパイ...
Pai Pa-Pa-Pai Pa-Pa-Pa-Yap-Pai...
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Pai Pai Kamen is a millionaire.
パッパッパヤッパ
Pa-pa-pa-ya-pa
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high.
踊れよ
Dance!
散々万歳コインシャワー
A disastrous banzai coin shower.
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the moment.
瞬間クライマックス
An instant climax.
浮世
Forget the fleeting world...
忘れて耽る
...and indulge yourself.
Dashing High High Ya Pai Ya
ディスコミュ系
Dis-communication style,
パイパイ仮面
Pai-pai Mask!
ディスコミュ系
Dis-communication style,
バイバイ仮面
Bye-bye Mask!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
DAY2！
DAY 2!
スタート！
Start!
DAY2！
DAY 2!
スタート！
Start!
じゃあ早速自己紹介からしていきますか？
Shall we start with self-introductions right away?
していきましょう！
Let's do it!
じゃあ皆 ぺこら久しぶりのあの挨拶行くから
Okay everyone, Pekora's gonna do that greeting for the first time in a while.
わかるよね皆！？
You know which one, right!?
あの挨拶だよ！
It's that greeting!
あれだ！
That one!
あれしかない！
It can only be that!
いくぞ！
Here we go!
ダダンガダンダンダン！全人類VTuber...
Dadanga-dandan-dan! All humanity VTuber...
全人...
All hum...
ドンマイ！
Don't mind!
あ 大丈夫か？
Ah, are you okay?
もう一度ね！
One more time!
いきます！
Let's go!
ぶん！
Bun!
ダダンガダンダンダン！
Dadanga-dandan-dan!
全VTuber一 超絶可愛いのは誰だ！？
Who is the cutest of all VTubers!?
ダダンガダンダンダン！
Dadanga-dandan-dan!
ぺこらちゃん！
Pekora-chan!
よー聞こえました！
I heard you loud and clear!
ありがと！
Thank you!
おー よー届きました！
Oh, it reached us well!
じゃあ次はフレア！
Next is Flare!
はい！じゃあフレアは...
Okay! So for Flare...
「Hi ダーリン」って言うので
I'll say 'Hi Darlin',
「Hi ハニー」って返してください！
So please reply with 'Hi Honey'!
いきますよ！
Here I go!
Hi ダーリン！
Hi Darlin'!
Hi ハニー！
Hi Honey!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生 不知火フレアです！
I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Gen!
そして？
And next?
はい えーどうしようかな...
Yes, uhm, what should I do...
えーじゃあ「こんまっする」って言うから
Well, I'll say 'Kon-muscle'...
普通に「こんまっする」...
...so just say 'Kon-muscle' normally...
まあ牛丼はまあ...バ...
Well, as for the beef bowl... wha...
あ やべやべ
Ah, crap, crap.
あばば
Ababa...
あばばばば
Ababababa.
よし いくぞ！
Alright, here I go!
せーの！
One, two!
こんまっするー！
Kon-muscle!
はい！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Yes! I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Gen!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
そして？
And?
君たち！
You guys!
本物のパイパイ仮面は...誰！？
Who is... the real Pai-pai Mask!?
船長！
Captain!
全然...なに？
Not at all... what?
なんか沸き上がらないけど...
You don't seem very excited though...
ねえ昨日からさ
Hey, since yesterday...
ぺこらに「船長」取られるし
...Pekora took 'Captain' from me,
ノエルに「パイパイ仮面」...
...and Noel took 'Pai-pai Mask'...
船長です！
I'm the Captain!
本物のパイパイ仮面は奪われたわけですね
So the real Pai-pai Mask was stolen, huh?
おー悲しい
Oh, how sad.
ということでね はい
Anyway, yes.
ホロライブ3期生 宝鐘海賊団船長の...
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates...
宝鐘マリンです！
Houshou Marine!
いや遂にDAY2！
Finally, DAY 2!
DAY2！
DAY 2!
DAY2ですよ！
It's DAY 2!
昨日と衣装違くない？
Isn't the outfit different from yesterday?
あれ？分かりましたか皆さん？
Oh? Did everyone realize?
なんか昨日とちょっと...
It's a bit different from yesterday...
悪魔になっちゃった
We became devils!
あら？ちょっと...
Oh my? A little...
悪魔っぽい？
...devilish?
小悪魔っぽい感じになってしまったかな？
Did we become like little devils?
そうなんですよね
That's right.
実はこれ 初めて公開するんですよね
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this.
そうなんですよ
That's right.
みんなビックリしたかな？
Was everyone surprised?
かわいい！
Cute!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
えーでも悪魔...
Eh, but devils...
なんかマリンは結構 小悪魔系で売ってるんで...
Marine markets herself as a 'Little Devil' type...
かなり親和性あるかな
...so there's a strong affinity.
本当に？
Really?
ぺこらも小悪魔系で売ってるから
Pekora also markets herself as a 'Little Devil' type.
船長？お前は悪魔
Captain? You're a Demon.
悪魔？ただの悪魔？
A Demon? Just a Demon?
変な悪魔
A weird Demon.
嫌な奴だな
What a jerk.
天使と悪魔 どっちが好き君たち？
Which do you guys like better, Angels or Devils?
あ 確かに
Ah, true.
じゃあ「はーい」で言ってもらえば？
Then ask them to say 'Yes'?
天使の人とか言って
Ask the Angel people.
ペンライトとか？
Use penlights?
色的に？
With colors?
じゃあ悪魔派は赤
Then, Devil faction is Red.
天使派は白
Angel faction is White.
せーの！
Ready, set!
掲げてください！
Raise them up!
綺麗 ほう 掲げて...
Beautiful... raise them...
あ でも結構いい感じに割れてる？
Ah, but it's split pretty evenly?
若干赤が多いか？
Maybe slightly more Red?
悪魔の方が人気？
Devils are more popular?
あ でも半々かも
Ah, but maybe half and half.
割れてるね
It's split.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあ今日 いいね 悪魔な感じも
Well, today is good, the Devil vibe too.
そうだね
That's right.
これを見てもらえてよかったぺこらね
I'm glad we could show this to you, Pekora.
よかった！
I'm glad!
そしてね DAY1に引き続き...
And continuing from DAY 1...
バンドも生演奏となってます！
The band is also performing live!
配信のコメントももちろん見てますからね！
We're checking the stream comments too, of course!
見てるよー！コメントのみんなー！
We see you! Everyone in the comments!
もうもちろん、会場のみんなももちろん！
And of course, everyone at the venue too!
当たり前やん！
That's a given!
見てるよー！すごい！
We see you! Amazing!
みんな素敵な気合いの入った
Thank you all for coming in your wonderful,
推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとう！
spirited fan-support fashion!
ありがとうー！可愛い！
Thank you! So cute!
最高、最高ですよ。最高ですね。
It's the best, truly the best.
いやもう初っ端ね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけど。
Well, we started right off with a shuffle medley.
すごーいよ！やばかったよね！
It was amazing! It was crazy, right?!
でもですね、なんとですね、ここままで...
But... actually... up to this point...
冒頭無料チラ見せが終了となります！
The free opening preview is ending!
えー！？そんなこと...嘘でしょ！？
Ehh?! No way... You're lying!?
嘘ってことでしょぺこ？
You're saying it's a lie, right peko?
そうなんです、嘘ではないぺこですね。
That's right, it is not a lie, peko.
みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、
I'm sure everyone wants to keep watching, so...
まあ概要欄に配信チケットのリンクあるので、
there is a link to the stream ticket in the description.
今！ポチポチっと買って見てください！
Right now! Click and buy it to watch!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
もう今日は...今日はもうぶち上がり！
Today... today is already super hyped!
もっとすごくなってます。
It's getting even more amazing.
もうぶち上げぶち上げで！
Yeah, hype hype!
Day1とは違ったね、良さが、盛り上がり。
The excitement is different from Day 1.
君たちも今日超ぶち上がりなんで、
You guys are super hyped today too, so...
頑張って最後まで息切れしないように、
Do your best not to run out of breath...
ぶち上がってください！
and stay hyped until the end!
しっかり声出してね！
Let us hear your voices clearly!
出してねー！
Let it out!
そしてね、配信で楽しんでる人は、
And for those enjoying the stream,
ハッシュタグ「きゅるるん大作戦Day2」で
please use the hashtag #KyururunOperationDay2...
いっぱい呟いてください！
and tweet a lot!
お願いしまーす！
Please!
ドキドキするね。
It's exciting.
そろそろ、次の曲に行ってもいいでしょうか？
Is it about time we go to the next song?
行ってみましょう！
Let's go!
ではですね、次の曲はなんと私から
Well then, for the next song...
スタートさせていただいても...
if I may start it off...
いいですか？
Is that okay?
じゃあ次の曲いきましょう！
Then let's go to the next song!
フレアメドレー！
Flare Medley!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.